We'll start by adding our call back functions
to our forecast fragment. Now know we have two
different options here for loader call backs. We want to
make sure that we're choosing the android.support.v4 callback so
we're compatible with Gingerbread. These take a generic
type. We're going to want to use cursor. And yes that
is Andriod.database.cursor. Now, let's move down to where we
want to actually insert this code. Here at the bottom
and, of course, we use control I to actually insert.
And there we have it beautifully, our loader pattern with cursor.
Now let's do some work that will help us out. First
we're [INAUDIBLE] of columns to the top of our forecast fragment.
These are the columns that are going to be used in our
query. Note, that since both weather entry and location entry have
the underscore ID field, we must fully qualify, which ID we
want in our projection for this query to work. And in
fact, this query requires a projection to work at
all, otherwise [UNKNOWN] ambiguous. Next, here are indexes that
are tied to these columns. This'll make some of
our work easier, later on. Note, that these actually must
match. Then we create some public indexes to use,
in our adapter. This allows us to make our
code tiny and efficient, in the adapter. But it
means, we must maintain the relationship between these column indexes.
And the projection. Each loader has an ID. It
allows a fragment to have multiple loaders active at
once. We're [INAUDIBLE] place this along with an instance
variable to save off our location here at the
top of our class. Next we're going to override
onActivityCreated. Loaders are initialized
in onActivityCreated because their life
cycle is actually bound to the activity. Not the
fragment. Note the use of the loader ID. FORECAST_LOADER.
Then we return to the onCreateLoader function.
We add a new CursorLoader. This CursorLoader has
our query, including start date, columns, and sort
order. Our start date is actually in our
URI. Our columns are the ones we defined earlier, and our sort order is going
to be based upon COLUMN_DATETEXT ascending. Let's do
one last check. We want to make sure we're
using the support library version of all of
these classes, otherwise we won't get Android 2.3 compatibility.